<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a Hello World JS Application">
   <intro href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm">
      <description>
         This cheat sheet shows you how to create the famous &quot;Hello World&quot; application and try it out. You will create a VJET project and a JavaScript File that will open a browser dialog with the text &quot;Hello world!&quot; when run.<br/>
<br/>
If you need help at any step, click the (?) to the right. Let&apos;s get started!
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open the VJET JS perspective" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/concepts/concepts-4.htm">
      <description>
         If you&apos;re not already in the VJET JS perspective, in the main menu select <b>Window</b> &gt; <b>Open Perspective</b> &gt; <b>VJET JS</b> or click on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=org.eclipse.dltk.mod.javascript.ui.JavascriptPerspective)"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a VJET JS Project" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.jdt.doc.user/concepts/concept-java-project.htm">
      <description>
         Before creating a JavaScript File, we need a project to put it in. In the main toolbar, click on the <b>New VJET JS Project</b> button, or click on the link below. Enter <b>HelloBrowser</b> for the project name, then	click <b>Finish</b>.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=org.ebayopensource.vjet.eclipse.ui.VJETProjectWizard)"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Create your HelloWorld Js File" dialog="true" skip="false" href="org.ebayopensource.vjet.eclipse.help/gettingStarted/basicTutorial/create_project.htm">
      <description>
         The next step is to create a new JS file In the main toolbar again, click on the <b>New JavaScript Source File</b> button (or the link below). If not already specified, select <b>HelloBrowser/src</b> as the source folder. Enter <b>HelloBrowser</b> for the file name, then click <b>Finish</b>.<br/>
<br/>
The VJET JS editor will automatically open showing your new JavaScript file
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=org.ebayopensource.vjet.eclipse.ui.JsFileCreation)"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Add a print statement" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/org.ebayopensource.vjet.eclipse.help/reference/editor/editor_layout.htm">
      <description>
         Now that you have your HelloWorld js add the following statement:<br/>
<br/>
alert(&quot;Hello browser!&quot;);<br/>
<br/>
Then <b>save</b> your changes; the Js file will automatically validate upon saving.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Run your VJET JS application" dialog="false" skip="false" href="/com.ebay.tools.vjet2.help/gettingStarted/basicTutorial/run_js.htm">
      <description>
         To <b>run</b> your application, right-click on your js file in the Script Explorer and select <b>Run As</b> &gt; <b>VJET  Browser Application</b>. The <b>Console</b> view should appear at the bottom and display the &quot;Hello, browser!&quot; output.<br/>
<br/>
Congratulations! You have successfully created a Hello Browser application!
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
